http://www.mysignshop.com/en_us/privacy-policy.html

This site uses cookies for various purposes including enhancing your experience, analytics,
and ads. By continuing to browse this site or by clicking "Accept and close", you
agree to our use of cookies. For more information, read our Cookies page.
Accept and close
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
To choose a language other than English or select your country of residence, please click here.
Welcome to Lexmark’s privacy page and thank you for your interest. Our program, Privacy@Lexmark, exists to help you understand what personal data we may collect and the steps we take to protect your privacy.  Lexmark strives to design products, services, processes, and solutions that ensure your personal data is properly handled and protected. To that end, we look to incorporate the following recognized privacy principles in everything we do:
Transparent notice and informed choice
Lawful use
Data Access
Data Integrity
Data Minimization
Data Security
Limited Sharing
Accountability for data transfers
Privacy@Lexmark is a dedicated organization whose sole purpose is to implement, promote, and maintain a corporate culture that understands and respects your right to privacy. If we can answer any questions or be of service to you in any way, please contact us as explained below.
Best regards,
Your P@L Team.
What is Personal Data?
Lexmark takes a broad view of Personal Data to best protect your privacy. Generally, the term “Personal Data” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable person (as opposed to a company or an organization). An identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by reference to things such as a name, an identification number, an address, an employee ID, job title, or a telephone number. For example, Jane Alvarez who lives at 123 Lexmark Lane with a telephone number of 859-123-4567 is an identifiable person:  her name, address, and telephone number are all examples of her Personal Data.  Other types of Personal Data can be less obvious—such as an IP address or other types of online identifiers.
Back to top
What is covered by this notice?
This notice covers all Personal Data collected in the use of our websites, our products and our services.  If in any case our privacy practices differ from those explained in this notice, we will advise you at the time we ask for your information.
Some pages on our websites may contain links to third-party websites. We do not endorse and have no control over the privacy practices or content of such websites. We recommend you carefully read the privacy notices of each site you visit – including ours.
Some products or solutions we offer may be co-branded or offered in conjunction with products or solutions from other companies. These products and solutions may come with other registration requests or terms and conditions. If you register or use these products, both we and the other company may receive the information you provide. While we carefully select our business partners, we do not endorse and have no control over the privacy practices or content of any third-party companies.
Back to top
When do we collect Personal Data?
We collect Personal Data when you contact or do business with Lexmark, such as when:
you make purchases of products or services;
you register products;
you request support for a product;
you request software downloads;
you create a user account (login user name and password);
you request information or materials (e.g., whitepapers or newsletters);
you participate in surveys and evaluations;
you participate in promotions, contests or giveaways;
you apply for a job or submit your resume;
you or someone you work for enters into a contract with us;
you submit questions or comments to us.
Back to top
What types of Personal Data do we collect?
We may collect various types of Personal Data, including:
your first and last name;
your title and your company's name;
your home, billing, or other physical address (including street name, name of a city or town, state/province, postal code);
your e-mail address;
your telephone number;
your educational background, employment experience, and job interest (for job applicants submitting information);
any other identifier that permits Lexmark to make physical or online contact with you;
information that we collect online from you and maintain in association with your account, such as your username and your password;
other information that you provide to us when you use our web shop or communicate with us.
We may also record the IP address you use to connect to the Internet. An IP address is a unique identifier used by devices to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet.
You do not need to provide us Personal Data simply to browse our site, but we do collect certain information using cookies and other technology as explained in our cookie notice.
If your Personal Data comes to us from a third party (for instance, from your employer), we require the third party to assure us they have the legal right to collect and provide us the data.
Lexmark does not actively market or target any communication to children or knowingly collect their information. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests.
Back to top
How do we use your information?
Like all companies, we use the Personal Data we collect in multiple ways. Examples include:
to operate our websites;
to fulfill your requests for information;
to register your products;
to process your job application;
to allow you to participate in contests and surveys;
to provide service and support,
to carry out the purchases you have requested;
to track your preferences related to our contact with you;
to provide you support and maintenance on your Lexmark products;
to fulfill our contractual responsibilities with your company.
We also use your Personal Data to communicate with you. We may use your Personal Data to send you certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, security warnings, software updates, and other support announcements.  If you choose to receive promotional materials from us we may also use your Personal Data to confirm that choice where necessary and to promote and market products, services, and special offers.
The Personal Data in our care may be stored, transferred, combined with other data, and otherwise processed, all in accordance with our privacy principles.
Back to top
Your rights
Your rights related to your Personal Data will vary by jurisdiction and may include:
The right to be fully informed of what data we collect, why we collect the data, and whether we intend to transfer it.
The right to access your data and correct or update any errors;
The right to erasure;
The right to notification;
The right to restrict the use of Personal Data;
The right to object to some forms of processing.
The right to lodge a complaint with the competent supervisory authority.
If our use of your Personal Data is based on your consent, you may withdraw it at any time by contacting us in writing as indicated below or, if applicable, through the Global Preference Center. We will inform you of the implications of withdrawing consent.
Back to top
How to contact us
Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this notice or our treatment of Personal Data by contacting us via the email address or the physical address indicated below. To ensure the most efficient handling of your issue, we highly encourage you to use the P@L email address. When we receive written questions and concerns, it is our policy to contact the individual user regarding his or her concerns as soon as reasonably possible. We will investigate and attempt to resolve any questions or concerns related to Personal Data or our privacy program in accordance with the principles contained in this notice.
E-mail
privacy@lexmark.com
Mail
Lexmark International, Inc.
Data Protection Officer
740 West New Circle Road
Lexington, Kentucky 40550
When you contact us please let us know your name, address, any email address you have provided on our website(s) and a description of the circumstances under which you provided the data (for example, to register a product, to receive a newsletter, etc.). To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before taking any action.
Back to top
Changes to this notice
We regularly review our compliance with this Privacy Notice. If we change this notice, we will post the revised notice here, along with the date of revision. If the changes are significant, we may also post a notice on our home page. Any changes will apply only from the date of the revision.
Back to top
Our privacy principles
The following sections provide a more detailed explanation of our privacy principles.
Notice of Personal Data use
It is Lexmark’s intent to be fully transparent in its collection and use of Personal Data. We provide notice when collecting your Personal Data to explain the purpose for which we are collecting the data.  This notice is intended to help you make an informed choice. We use our best efforts to provide information and an explanation in a clear and convenient manner at every point we ask for your data.
We provide notice regarding the types of data we collect, how the data will be used, how the data is obtained (if it is not already clear), with whom the data may be shared, and how long it will be retained. An example may be found in our Global Preference Center. If we have not been clear or you have any question or concern, please ask.
We will not use the data for any purpose other than as provided in the notice. If you or your employer choose to have a contractual or other business relationship with Lexmark, we may contact you in connection with that business relationship when necessary.
Most of the time, you may simply choose not to provide us your Personal Data. If you choose not to provide the Personal Data we request online, you can still visit most of our web pages, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.
Back to top
Lawful use
Depending on the circumstances under which we collect Personal Data, Lexmark’s use and processing of the data is based on one or more of the following:
your consent;
fulfillment of an obligation to you;
our compliance with an applicable law, regulation, or other legal obligation;
a need to protect your or another natural person’s vital interests; or,
our company`s or a third party’s legitimate interests where such interest overrides your personal interest, fundamental rights or freedoms.
Lexmark frequently reviews the purposes for which data is collected to ensure that our data collection supports reasonable business requirements.
Back to top
Data access
Your personal data belongs to you. We will provide you as much access and information as we reasonably can to update or amend the Personal Data in our care. Where applicable, we also provide a method to withdraw your consent, request a copy or transfer of your data, and even delete your Personal Data. Please keep in mind that any such request must be valid and legal and we may require additional details from you to respond appropriately. We will respond to each request in accordance with the law.
Back to top
Data integrity
Lexmark takes reasonable steps to ensure that the Personal Data we process is accurate, complete and current by encouraging you to update your Personal Data as necessary.
We strive to keep your Personal Data accurately recorded. We have implemented technology, management processes, and policies to help maintain data accuracy. We provide individuals with reasonable access to review and correct their Personal Data.
Back to top
Data minimization
Lexmark’s practice is to gather the least amount of Personal Data required for the stated purpose. It is also our policy to retain any Personal Data only as long as required to meet the business need for which it is collected. Once the business need has expired, the Personal Data will be routinely deleted. In some cases, Personal Data must be retained longer than either of us may expect due to legal obligations.
Back to top
Data security
We take seriously the trust you place in us and work hard to incorporate information security into our systems, our products, and our services. We employ a global team of security professionals that sets standards and governs the enforcement of a number of corporate policies.
To protect against unauthorized access, misuse, disclosure, or alteration of your Personal Data, we employ appropriate physical, technical, organizational, and administrative measures.
Lexmark products and services are designed with privacy and security in mind using tested methodologies such as a Secure Development Lifecycle and Privacy Impact Assessments. Our devices have received worldwide recognition year after year for their robust security options and our organization has received security related certifications such as ISO 27001.
Back to top
Sharing data
We keep your Personal Data confidential. We will not sell, rent, trade or lease your Personal Data to others. Unless we have your permission, we will not use or share your Personal Data in ways unrelated to the ones we describe at the time you provide the data or as described in a controlling contract. We engage service providers and suppliers (“agents”) to perform certain functions on our behalf. For example, these agents may deliver products to you, provide product service and support, maintain our information technology systems, and assist us with legitimate marketing and communication initiatives. Those agents will be permitted to process Personal Data only to perform the services specified by Lexmark. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose. Any agent will have entered into written terms with Lexmark requiring that the agent abide by terms no less protective than Lexmark`s own privacy standards.
Lexmark or its affiliates could merge with or be acquired by another business, or their respective assets may be acquired. Lexmark will seek appropriate protection for personal information in these types of transactions
Back to top
Cross-border transfers
We are a global organization with offices and customers around the world. To efficiently manage our business and best serve you, all kinds of data – not just Personal Data – may be transferred and accessed by Lexmark entities worldwide on the basis of this Privacy Notice and in alignment with international data privacy standards.   We may store, transfer, and process Personal Data in the United States and other countries where we maintain facilities.  By using our websites or services you consent to any such transfer of information outside your country
Back to top
California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, you may have rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018.  To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit the Lexmark Privacy Notice for California Residents.
Back to top
